twinspires.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Churchill Downs Incorporated

**Churchill Downs Incorporated and its subsidiary companies ("CDI", "we" or "us") have adopted this Privacy Policy to establish and maintain an adequate level of protection for your Personal data.**

This Privacy Policy explains how we protect your privacy and the confidentiality of the information that you provide to us when you use CDI’s websites and related products and services. **  By accessing and/or using this website, or any Churchill Downs Incorporated service, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT:**

**Personal Information (which you provide to us)**

You may register or open an account with CDI on any CDI managed website if you are at least eighteen (18) years old, (older in some jurisdictions for account wagering).

CDI may collect some or all of the following "Personal Information" voluntarily provided by you during certain site registration and account funding processes:

  * Your Name, address, date of birth, phone number and email address
  * Your Social Security Number
  * Your bank and/or credit card account number

CDI does not give out your Personal Information to any third party for uses not described as normal business operations.

**Other Information (which we collect about you)**

CDI may collect the following other Information about you when you interact with our online services:

  * Your computer IP address, and browser history on our sites
  * Your e-mail address
  * Information volunteered by you, such as survey information and/or site registrations, user id and passwords
  * Purchases made by you on our site(s)
  * Your wagering activity (identified by your account number and name)
  * If you choose to connect to our sites through a social network such as Facebook or Twitter, we may collect your profile information
  * The physical location of the computer from which you are accessing Churchill Downs Incorporated Services.

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION:**

We use your Personal Information to fulfill the purpose for which you provide it to us, including, but not limited to verifying your identity, to fulfill your wagering activity or process purchases made on our websites.

CDI uses your Personal Information in order to ensure that wagering activity on our sites meets various state and federal laws and other statutory requirements.  In addition, from time to time we may use your Personal Information to contact you regarding promotions and marketing offers and other purposes which are generally limited to our services. You have the opportunity when registering and at any point thereafter to withdraw your consent to receive electronic promotions by clicking “unsubscribe” in any email you receive from CDI.

Personal and other information may be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies in response to warrants, subpoenas or other governmental orders. You are hereby advised that in the event of a criminal investigation by state or federal authorities or regulatory inquiry, you waive any and all rights to account holder information and data in CDI's possession, and you specifically authorize CDI to disclose said data and information to law enforcement authorities. In this situation, you agree to release Churchill Downs Incorporated and its affiliated companies from any and all liability related to such disclosure, to the fullest extent permissible by law.

From time to time, CDI may share information we collect about you with third parties, in an aggregate and confidential form only, in order to assist with marketing or other normal business activities.  We contractually require these companies to use your personal information only for the purpose of providing a particular product or service to you or us, and do not authorize them to use your personal information for any other reason.   ** **

**Public Postings (Forums, Chat Rooms, Message Boards)**

Please note that information you post in a chat room, a message board, a forum or another public posting area on our websites or social media can be viewed by anyone with internet access. Please do not disclose personal information in public posting areas. CDI is not responsible for a third party's use of information which you post in a public area.

**Personalized Advertising**

Like many other websites, we use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies (“cookies”) to enable us to provide you with more relevant advertising.  Cookies are small, removable data files that are placed on your computer’s internet web browser.  These cookies work to remember that you visited our website.   When you later visit a third-party website, ads related to our websites might be displayed.  In the simplest of terms, the cookies allow third parties to display relevant ads to you based on your past visit to our website.  We do not provide your personal information to advertisers or third-party websites that display our personalized ads. 

**Children's  Guidelines**

None of CDI’s websites is directed towards children under the age of thirteen (13) and we will not knowingly collect or use any information from any person identified as being under the age of thirteen (13).

**Third-Party Sites**

We use third parties to process purchases, including but not limited to, gift shop items, ticketing and hotel reservations.  CDI includes links to other websites whose privacy practices we do not control.

Information you provide on another website is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of that site. These websites may have privacy policies and practices that differ from ours.

We may use third-party advertisers to serve advertisements on CDI websites. Our advertisers may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to, among other things, to enable our advertisers to monitor the ads you have viewed on our site.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY:**

To ensure site security and network performance, CDI monitors all inbound and outbound network traffic in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload and change information, or otherwise cause damage or conduct criminal activity. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to our services are strictly prohibited and shall be punishable under applicable state or federal law. Please be advised, however, that the Internet and various networking communication mediums are not secure, unless explicitly stated as such, and may be subject to interception or loss which is beyond the control of CDI.

We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information during certain of your online interactions with us. We utilize procedures to protect confidential information off-line, as well. We restrict access to your Personal Information to employees who need the information to perform a specific task for you or us. Our employees use password-protected log-ins to access CDI’s computer servers to protect against unauthorized access, acquisition, destruction, use, modification or disclosure of information. The servers which hold personally identifiable information are maintained in a locked, secure hosting environment. 

DO NOT TRACK:  Do Not Track (DNT) is an optional browser setting that allows you to express your preferences regarding tracking by advertisers and other third parties.  We do not currently respond to DNT signals. 

**Data Integrity**

CDI processes personal information only for the purposes and transactions for which it was collected and in accordance with this privacy policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary **.** ****

Your data will be subject to purge from our storage system after the purpose for which the data was collected is satisfied and/or approximately five years of inactivity.

**Ability to Access Personal Information**

Any questions you may have regarding our Privacy Policy, the accuracy of your personal or non-personal information, or the use of your personal or non-personal information, or any requests that we correct, update, or remove your information in our databases, should be done so by contacting us through this website or by sending a letter with your name, address and telephone number to the following address:

Webmaster  
CDI Information Request  
Churchill Downs Incorporated  
600 N. Hurstbourne Parkway  
Suite 400  
Louisville, KY 40222

Telephone: 502/636-4400, or toll free 800/283-3729  
Email:  [webmaster@kyderby.com](mailto:webmaster@kyderby.com)

A CDI representative will follow up by mail or phone with you.

**Opt-Out Policy for CDI Solicitations**

You may opt out of receiving advertising and general information e-mails from CDI that are not associated with your account by contacting the CDI Webmaster and specifying that you want to opt out, or unsubscribe, to receiving advertising and general information emails from CDI.  We provide an “unsubscribe” link in every email advertisement.

If you are unable to “unsubscribe” from unwanted emails through the “unsubscribe” link, please contact webmaster@kyderby directly.

**Text Messages**

If you agree to receive text messages from CDI, we may use an automatic telephone dialing system to contact you. You are not required to consent to receive text messages in order to obtain products or services from CDI. Standard messaging rates apply. We may send you up to four (4) texts per month. If you would like to stop receiving text messages at any time you can reply to any message with the word "STOP". We may send you one additional confirmatory message to let you know that we’ve received your request.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you may contact:

Webmaster  
Churchill Downs Incorporated  
600 N. Hurstbourne Parkway, Suite 400  
Louisville, KY 40222  
Telephone: 502/636-4400, or toll free 800/283-3729  
Email:  [webmaster@kyderby.com](mailto:webmaster@kyderby.com)

**Changes**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March, 2018.  CDI reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.  Any significant changes to this Privacy Policy will be noted as such on this website and emailed to our customers on file.
